YURIY KOSHYK

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

As a skilled UX/UI Designer and Frontend Developer, I bring digital projects to life through user-centered design principles, user research, and frontend development expertise. With proficiency in React, I am experienced in building responsive, crossbrowser-compatible, and accessible web applications.

PORTFOLIO



@YURIYKOSH

+420 776 182 501

@YURIY_KOSH

Bē

@YURIYKOSH



@YURIY-KOSHYK

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

SOYUMMY [HTML, SASS, ReactJS, Redux, React Router, Axios, Webpack]

Role: Scrum Master / Developer.

YURIY.KOSHYK@GMAIL.COM

Application to find, add, share, and organize cooking recipes.

Help the team of 8 members work together effectively, overcome any problems that came up.

FILMOTEKA [HTML, SASS, JS, REST API, AJAX, Firebase, Parcel]

Role: Team Lead.

Application for choosing a movie.

Build project on github, check for build errors and live page performance.

EVENTPOS [Figma, Adobe Creative Suite]

Role: UX/UI Designer.

Mobile payment solution specifically designed for events.

Designed and developed the overall concept, functionality, and UX of a product.

SKILLS

HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS UX/UI design JavaScript / TypeScript React

Redux

REST API

AJAX

Webpack / Vite / Parcel

Node.js

GIT

PHP

Figma

Adobe Creative Suite

WORK HISTORY

FRONTEND DEVELOPER & UX/UI DESIGNER

Heimdal Data ApS | Dec 2022 - current

- · Develop user-friendly interfaces with a focus on user experience.
- · Write clean and scalable code for website performance.
- · Conduct user research and gather requirements for the design process.
- · Stay up-to-date with new technologies and design trends.
- · Adhere to UX/UI design standards and collaborate with stakeholders.

UX/UI DESIGNER

Freelance | Mar 2022 - Dec 2022

- · Gather and evaluate user requirements
- · Design graphical UI elements
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes
- · Identify and troubleshoot UX problems
- · Adhere to style standards

SOFT SKILLS

Attention to details Creativity Communication Skills Problem-solving Time management

EDUCATION

Frontend Developer IT School GoIT | 2022 - 2023



Media Communications Diploma

Humber College | 2020 - 2022



B Foundation in Computing

Bournemouth University International College | 2016 - 2017